Guide to the Eldon Dedini Papers
The Ohio State University Billy Ireland Cartoon Library & Museum
- Series VII. Roughs, Sketches, and Drawings, 1950-2005
  This series contains Dedini's rough work, sketches, and drawings created for various publications and projects. There's a large amount of roughs for his gags involving Russia, Communism, and particularly Vladmir Lenin.
  - Roy Williams, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 24)
  - Ink Sketches, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 25)
  - Dedini Gallery, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 26)
  - Randy Reinstedt, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 27)
  - Wine Labels and Rich Hughett Wine, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 28)
  - Wine Festival, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 29)
  - Working Xeroxes of Roughs, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 30)
  - Character Sketches, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 31)
  - Doodles, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 32)
  - Panels/Early Ink Sketches, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 33)
  - Dick Crispo, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 34)
  - Big City Wind in the Willows, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 35)
  - Sketchbooks (10 Volumes), Undated (Box ED 37, Folder 1-10)
  - Drawings (2 Folders), Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 1-2)
  - Drawings to Ohio State, Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 3)
  - Painting and Drawing Notes, Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 4)
  - Satyrs, Undated (Box ED 36, Folder 4)
  - Lenin by Dedini, Undated (Box ED 36, Folder 5)
  - Xeroxes (color copies, birthday cards), 2002-2003 (Box ED 36, Folder 6)
  - Early Gag Roughs, Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 5)
  - Gag Roughs, 1992 (Box ED 38, Folder 6)
  - Pen Sketches (Pica and Others), Undated (Box ED 39, Folder 1)
  - Studies for Poster Exhibit Arriola/ Dedini/ Ketcham, Undated (Box ED 39, Folder 2)
  - Early Christmas Roughs for Various Publications, Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 6)
  - Xmas/ New Year Doodles and Notes, Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 7)
  - Christmas Roughs, Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 9)
  - Roughs, Rework/ Maybe, Good Scenes/ Good Drawing, 1980-1983 (Box ED 38, Folder 10)
  - Ideas, Scenes, Gags, etc., Roughs, 1970-1980 (Box ED 38, Folder 11)
  - Roughs- Words, 1970-1980 (Box ED 38, Folder 12)
  - Betty Boop Roughs, Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 13)
  - Boy-Girl Roughs, Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 14)
  - Ukiyo-e Japanese Wood Block Idea, Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 15)
  - Finish Roughs, Possible, Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 16)
  - Now! (clippings/roughs), Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 17)
  - Gags-Slips-Notes Early (laughs), Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 18)
  - Art Notes Beginning 1977 (Box ED 38, Folder 19)
  - Lunowels (roughs), Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 20)
  - Doodles, October 1983 (Box ED 38, Folder 21)
  - Doodles, June 1982 (Box ED 38, Folder 22)
  - Words, 1982-1984 (Box ED 38, Folder 23)
  - Notes and Roughs, 1957-1958 (Box ED 38, Folder 24)
  - Barbara Shermunds Published with Dedini Gags (collaboration), Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 25)
  - Lenin (2 Folders), Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 26-27)
  - Untitled roughs, Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 28)
  - Words, Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 29)
  - Residue of Thoughts Edited from 1977-79, 1977-1979 (Box ED 38, Folder 30)
  - Untitled roughs, Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 31)
  - Doodles worth fooling with (roughs), Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 32)
  - Old, but good scenes (roughs), Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 33)
  - Music Gags (roughs), Undated (Box ED 38, Folder 34)
  - Ideas, Comic, and Fine Art (clippings/roughs), Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 1)
  - Grit Pics, Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 2)
  - Ugrudz 2 (roughs), Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 3)
  - Drawings, Paintings, Nudes, Etc. (roughs), Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 4)
  - Old Gags (roughs), Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 5)
  - Special Gags (roughs), Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 6)
  - Try Again- Good Scenes- Try New Lines (roughs), Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 7)
  - Roughs (4 Folders), Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 8-11)
  - Minotaurs, Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 12)
  - Erotic Japan, Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 13)
  - Ted Gargiulo "Songs My Father Taught Me", Undated (Box ED 39, Folder 3)
  - Rejects, Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 14)
  - Computer, Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 15)
  - Microvideo, Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 16)
  - Not Used, Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 17)
  - Satyrs and Satyr History (2 Folders), Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 18-19)
  - Sex/ Playboy-type Subject Material (roughs), Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 20)
  - Roughs, April- May 1987 (Box ED 40, Folder 21)
  - Business Gags/ Computers, Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 22)
  - Gags, Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 23)
  - Gags- Space (3 Folders), Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 24-26)
  - Russian Roughs (3 Folders), Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 27-29)
  - Art Ideas, Gags, Roughs, Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 30)
  - Golf Gags- Sam Gross, Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 31)
  - Books- Sam Gross, Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 32)
  - Movies- Sam Gross, Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 33)
  - Lawyer Joke Book and Gags, 2003 (Box ED 40, Folder 34)
  - Gags on Restaurant Cooking, Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 35)
  - Roka, Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 36)
  - Roughs, Russian- Nadia, Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 37)
  - Lenin, 1987 (Box ED 40, Folder 38)
  - Lenin Doodles, Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 39)
  - Lenin Xeroxes/Album Notes/Lenin in Coconino County, Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 40)
  - Mock-up of Cartoons Related to the Soviet Union, Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 41)
  - Lenin notes, sketches, thoughts, doodles, Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 42)
  - Lenin Notes/Gags, 1983-1987, Undated (Box ED 40, Folder 43)
  - Lenin Sketches, Undated (Box ED 39, Folder 4)
  - Jazz Posters and Other Ideas, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 1)
  - Concours Posters- Notes and Ideas, 1976 (Box ED 41, Folder 2)
  - Christmas Notes, Faith-Based Roughs, 2001 (Box ED 41, Folder 3)
  - Xmas Idea Sketches (Playboy) Roughs, 1996 (Box ED 41, Folder 4)
  - Special Spread, Cartoon Angles, 1970s (Box ED 41, Folder 5)
  - Not Yet Sent- In the Works Roughs, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 6)
  - Face Doodles, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 7)
  - Picasso Follies Roughs, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 8)
  - Christmas CartooR roughs, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 9)
  - Xmas Roughs, 2005 (Box ED 41, Folder 10)
  - Xmas Notes and Other Doodles, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 11)
  - Paining; Thoughts for Dedini; Lenin; Social Political Art, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 12)
  - Caricatures of Reagan, Oval Office, 1980s (Box ED 41, Folder 13)
  - Roughs for Robert Talbott, Correspondence and Receipts, 1979-1982 (Box ED 41, Folder 14)
  - Panel Roughs, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 15)
  - Buzz Rainier Roughs, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 16)
  - Ecology Humor Roughs, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 17)
  - Monterey Life Magazine, Roughs and Ideas, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 18)
  - Comic Strips (for Playboy Parodies and Playboy Funnies), 1978-1979 (Box ED 41, Folder 19)
  - Spring Humor Roughs, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 20)
  - Golf, Stu Heinecke, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 21)
  - Golf Ideas- Clips and Roughs, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 22)
  - Ideas, Notes, and Roughs, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 23)
  - Notes, Francis Bacon, Lenin, Reminders, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 24)
  - Roughs (2 Folders), Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 25-26)
  - Gags, Clips, Sketches in the Works, Stuff, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 27)
  - Notes on Roughs, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 28)
  - Faces, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 29)
  - Faces, Men, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 30)
  - Word Ideas, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 31)
  - Now- Roughs, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 32)
  - Rough Gags, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 33)
  - Roughs (NY), 1996 (Box ED 41, Folder 34)
  - Words, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 35)
  - Roughs- Playboy, 2004 (Box ED 41, Folder 36)
  - Playboy Roughs, Scenes, Gags, Notes, Some sent, February 2001 (Box ED 41, Folder 37)
  - Roughs and Interesting Pics (Possible for Playboy), Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 38)
  - Playboy Roughs, Clips, Notes, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 39)
  - Doodles, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 40)
  - Okayed Roughs for Various Publications, Notes and Rejection Slips (Some Color), Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 41)
  - Playboy Roughs (some in color), Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 42)
  - Okayed Roughs and Captions for Playboy and Other Publications, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 43)
  - Roughs in Color, Xmas and Others, Undated (Box ED 41, Folder 44)
  - Roughs Okayed, Undated (Box ED 42, Folder 1)
  - Roughs Okayed (some in color, possible Playboy), Undated (Box ED 42, Folder 2)
  - Roughs (Includes rough for Playboy New Year with a handwritten note by Hugh Hefner), Undated (Box ED 42, Folder 3)
  - Doodles, includes computer gags, Undated (Box ED 42, Folder 4)
  - Doodles (some cover ideas), Undated (Box ED 42, Folder 5)
  - Doodles- Playboy, Undated (Box ED 42, Folder 6)
  - Doodles, Portraits/Caricatures of Artists, Undated (Box ED 42, Folder 7)
  - Doodles of Historical Figures and Others, Undted (Box ED 42, Folder 8)
  - Doodles of Birthdays "Nebuchadnezzar for 2", Undated (Box ED 42, Folder 9)
  - Doodles, Max Shulman Illustrations, Undated (Box ED 42, Folder 10)
  - Doodles (2 Folders), Undated (Box ED 42, Folder 11-12)
  - Doodles- Art, People, Posters, NY Covers, etc., Undated (Box ED 42, Folder 13)
  - Doodles- People, Undated (Box ED 42, Folder 14)
  - Sold Roughs with Notes from Hugh Hefner and Michelle Urry, Undated (Box ED 42, Folder 15)
  - Okayed Roughs (New Yorker and Playboy), Undated (Box ED 42, Folder 16)
  - Dedini Xmas Card Roughs, Undated (Box ED 42, Folder 17)
  - Do! Spreads, Stories Page Ideas (New Yorker), Undated (Box ED 42, Folder 18)
  - Roughs, 1989 (Box ED 42, Folder 19)
  - Gag Notes, Good Lines and Doodles, 1991 (Box ED 42, Folder 20)
  - Roughs, 1991 (Box ED 42, Folder 21)
  - Okayed Roughs, Undated (Box ED 42, Folder 22)
  - Dedini Signature Doodles, Undated (Box ED 42, Folder 23)
  - Film Festival Posters and Notes, 1970 (Box ED 42, Folder 24)
  - Jazz Poster and Other Dedini Ideas, Undated (Box ED 42, Folder 25)
  - Poster Ideas- Jazz and Other Events, Undated (Box ED 42, Folder 26)
  - Xeroxes of Dedini Illustrations, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 3)
  - Dedini Caricatures- Satyrs, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 4)
  - Sixteenth Annual Concours d' Elegance, Poster Color Separations Transparencies, 1966 (Map-case AC.AH7.001)
  - Seventeenth Annual Concours d' Elegance, Poster Color Separations Transparencies, 1967 (Map-case AC.AH7.002)
  - Cannery Row Angels "Dora Flood" Kalisa M and Bettina H., drawings, sketches, and notes, 2002 (Map-case AC.AH6.004)
  - Amacom/ Gargiulo Cover, 2005 (Map-case AC.AH6.005)
  - Hans Lehmann Book Jacket, 2001 (Map-case AC.AH6.006)
- Series VIII. Original Art, Undated
  This series contains the original art work by Eldon Dedini it has been described on the items level in the original art database. To view catalog records of the Billy Ireland Cartoon Library & Museum holdings of Eldon Dedini's original art work, please see the Original Art Database.
- Series IX. Research Files, 1950s-2000s, Undated
  This is the largest series in the collection and contains all of Dedini's resource materials for research purposes. Dedini was a voracious reader throughout his career and looked to newspapers, magazines, and books to inspire his cartoons. There is a large amount of research files for wine, Russia, Playboy, and the New Yorker. Books, magazines, other published materials from Dedini's library can also be found in The Ohio State University Libraries
  - Renault (Clipped Comics), Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 1)
  - Picture Files (Soviet Union), Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 2-3)
  - Print Mint- Underground Comics, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 4)
  - Cartoonists, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 5-6)
  - Gardner- Other Gag Writers, 1950s-2000 (Box ED 43, Folder 7)
  - Art Clips (Kalisa), Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 8)
  - Irving Penn Photos of New Yorker Cartoonists, Undated (Box ED 39, Folder 5)
  - The Rustler, Newspaper, King City, CA, 1979-1984 (Box ED 44, Folder 1)
  - The Rustler Newspaper- Section "The Land" pictures, his and people of region, 1979-1984 (Box ED 44, Folder 2)
  - News clippings about Monterey History, 1976-1978 (Box ED 44, Folder 3)
  - Stonehenge, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 9)
  - Tango, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 10)
  - Dance, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 11)
  - Arab World, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 12)
  - Men-Women, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 13)
  - Japan, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 15)
  - Fred Martin, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 15)
  - Hugh Hefner, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 16)
  - Great Stuff, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 17)
  - Clint Eastwood, 1980s-1990s (Box ED 43, Folder 18)
  - New Yorker Old Notes, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 19)
  - Balthus, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 20)
  - Pop Art, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 21)
  - Ballet, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 22)
  - Fuseli, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 22)
  - Stuff, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 24)
  - Saul Steinberg, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 25)
  - Italian Paintings, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 26)
  - Spanish Paintings, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 27)
  - Flemish Paintings, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 28)
  - Russian Avant Guard [sic], Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 29)
  - Early American Art, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 30)
  - Surrealism, Dali, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 31)
  - Cezanne, Undated (Box ED 43, Folder 32)
  - Jean Baptiste Millet, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 1)
  - Giotto, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 2)
  - Mexican Art, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 3)
  - Persian Art, Iran, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 4)
  - Carl Hanson, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 5)
  - Fucking, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 6)
  - Subject-War, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 7)
  - Civilization, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 8)
  - Clips/Ideas, July 1982-Sept. 1983 (Box ED 45, Folder 9)
  - Essays, 1960s-1970s (Box ED 45, Folder 10)
  - Sydney Harris, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 11)
  - Andrew Wyeth, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 12)
  - Calvin and Hobbes, Gary Larson, Gary Trudeau, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 13)
  - Russia, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 14)
  - Films 60s and 70s, 1960s-1970s (Box ED 45, Folder 15)
  - Aquarium, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 15)
  - Russell Baker, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 17)
  - Latino, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 18)
  - Robert Raushenburg, 1977 (Box ED 45, Folder 19)
  - Big Bang and Other Theories, Science, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 20)
  - Scenes, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 21)
  - Barnett-Newman, 1977 (Box ED 45, Folder 22-23)
  - China, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 24)
  - Interiors Ordinary, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 25)
  - Clothes-People, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 26)
  - Men-Bachrach-Other Men Catalogs, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 27)
  - Dennis Renault, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 28)
  - Art and Reviews, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 29)
  - Sophia Loren, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 30)
  - Pebble Beach Mansions, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 31)
  - Marilyn Monroe, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 32)
  - Brigitte Bardot, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 33)
  - Nostalgia News Clips, Undated (Box ED 45, Folder 34)
  - Robert Talbot Ties, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 1)
  - Adult Material, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 2)
  - Art Clips and Essays, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 3)
  - Wonderful Cornball Scenes! Landscapes, lone cypress, everything and anything, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 4)
  - Jules Feiffer, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 5)
  - Tom Friedman and Others Articles, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 6-7)
  - Good Stuff, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 8)
  - Interesting Articles, 2001 (Box ED 46, Folder 9)
  - Switzerland, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 10)
  - Iraq, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 11)
  - Iraq Cartoons, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 12)
  - Fareed Zakaria, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 13)
  - Identity Theft, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 14)
  - Islam, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 15)
  - Kerry-Bush-Clinton, 2004 (Box ED 46, Folder 16)
  - People, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 17-18)
  - Poster Notes, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 19)
  - Thoughts on the Business of Life Articles, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 20)
  - Words, Clips, Essays, Xmas Sources, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 21)
  - Xmas Playboy, New Years, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 22-23)
  - Xmas Misc. Clips, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 24-25)
  - Xmas Clips, 1994 (Box ED 46, Folder 26)
  - Xmas Scenes, Essays, History, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 27)
  - Idea Clips, Various Years, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 28)
  - Photos, Movie Studio Stills, 1930s (Box ED 46, Folder 29)
  - Clint Eastwood as Mayor of Carmel-by-the-Sea, 1986-1988 (Box ED 46, Folder 30)
  - CCCP, Undated (Box ED 46, Folder 31)
  - Art Critics, 1946-1948 (Box ED 47, Folder 1)
  - Russia 1992 Transition (Box ED 47, Folder 2)
  - Lenin, Gorbachev, CCCP, Kremlin, 1985; 1987 (Box ED 47, Folder 3)
  - Socialism, Undated (Box ED 47, Folder 4)
  - Russia (basic background scenes), Undated (Box ED 47, Folder 5)
  - Clips, Russia, 1993 (Box ED 47, Folder 6)
  - Solzhenitsyn, Undated (Box ED 47, Folder 7)
  - Current Clips, 2003-2004 (Box ED 47, Folder 8)
  - New Yorker Clips Ideas, Undated (Box ED 47, Folder 9)
  - Clips, 1997 (Box ED 47, Folder 10-18)
  - Future, Undated (Box ED 47, Folder 19)
  - Metropolitan Diary Articles, Undated (Box ED 47, Folder 20)
  - Pics, Undated (Box ED 47, Folder 21)
  - Star Wars, Undated (Box ED 47, Folder 22)
  - Y2K, Undated (Box ED 47, Folder 23)
  - Monterey- Carmel, Undated (Box ED 47, Folder 24-25)
  - Comic Books, Undated (Box ED 47, Folder 26)
  - Black Panthers, Undated (Box ED 47, Folder 27)
  - Essays: Time, Newsweek, 2005 (Box ED 48, Folder 1)
  - Sex, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 2)
  - History of AIDS, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 3)
  - Art Clips, Thoughts, Themes, Whatever, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 4)
  - Art, Great Articles for Ideas & Cartoons, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 5)
  - Artists Dialogue, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 6)
  - Art, Paintings, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 7)
  - Art and Articles, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 8)
  - Cinema- Sideways, 2004 (Box ED 48, Folder 9)
  - Clips, political, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 10)
  - Clips Now, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 11)
  - Comedy- Steve Martin, Lenny Bruce, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 12)
  - Comic Books/Manga, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 13)
  - Assorted Comic Strips, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 14)
  - Dance, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 15)
  - Diet, eat smart, etc., Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 16)
  - Spring/Summer Idea Starters, 2002-2003 (Box ED 48, Folder 17)
  - Films, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 18)
  - Forbes, ideas, bizness [sic], scenes, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 19)
  - Goofy, out of context clips, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 20)
  - Idea Starters, columns, newspaper, editorials, 2000s (Box ED 48, Folder 21)
  - Interiors, 1980s-1990s (Box ED 48, Folder 22)
  - Jazz, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 23)
  - Ben Katchor, 1999 (Box ED 48, Folder 24)
  - Lions/Pumas, CA, 2004 (Box ED 48, Folder 25)
  - Madonna, 1990s (Box ED 48, Folder 26)
  - New Mafia, 2001 (Box ED 48, Folder 27)
  - New Yorker Clips and Photos, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 28)
  - New Yorker Cartoonists Roughs, by other artists, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 29)
  - Photos, NY Times & Others (Life as its lived), Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 30)
  - Playboy Themes of Now, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 31)
  - Political Cartoons, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 32-34)
  - Poses/Nudes, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 35)
  - Bars, Restaurants, Scenes, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 36)
  - Russia, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 37)
  - Scams, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 39)
  - Arnold Schwartzenegger as Gov., 2003 (Box ED 48, Folder 39)
  - Thomas Sowell Columns, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 40)
  - Sports, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 41)
  - Stuff, clips about everything, photos, articles, jazz, etc., Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 42)
  - Thoughts on the Business of Life, Undated (Box ED 48, Folder 43-44)
  - Turkey, 1996 (Box ED 49, Folder 1)
  - W, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 2)
  - Wine, Bin Sacca Label, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 3)
  - Fine Arts Clips, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 4)
  - Joan Didion, Woody Allen, Swifty Lazar, Fashion, Anne Klein, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 6)
  - Restaurant Reviews, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 7)
  - Current Restaurants, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 8)
  - Carmel Festival, 2004 (Box ED 49, Folder 9)
  - Carmel History, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 10)
  - Children's Books, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 11)
  - Clinton Impeachment, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 12)
  - Cowpokes, 1983 (Box ED 49, Folder 13)
  - Joan Didion, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 14)
  - Earthquake Info, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 15)
  - Ecology, Greenhouse Effect, 1988-1989 (Box ED 49, Folder 16)
  - Fuad Bahou, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 17)
  - Future Idea Starters, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 18)
  - Future/Past Idea Starters, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 19)
  - Immigrants, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 20)
  - Junipero Serra, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 21)
  - Ketcham- From Menace to Matisse; Hank Ketcham's 75th Bday Celebration, 1995 (Box ED 49, Folder 22)
  - Articles by Lisa Crawford Watson, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 23)
  - Man- Woman idea starters, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 24)
  - Martin Meursault, Table Talk articles, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 25)
  - Funny Names, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 26)
  - Photography Notes, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 27)
  - Posters, Brad Hollan, notes etc., prints, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 28)
  - Rick Deragon & other local art clips, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 29)
  - Russian Clips, 1980s (Box ED 49, Folder 30)
  - SFMOMA, 1995-1996 (Box ED 49, Folder 31)
  - Stonepine Estate & Resort, 1988 (Box ED 49, Folder 32)
  - Wine Festivals, lists of good wine, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 33-34)
  - Women's Liberation Early, Undated (Box ED 49, Folder 35)
  - Art Galleries, Metropolitan Museum, Vatican, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 1)
  - Artists and Prints, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 2)
  - Artists Studios, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 3)
  - Ann Landers & other wisdom, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 5-6)
  - Drugs, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 7)
  - Epic of Medicine, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 8)
  - Existentialism, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 9)
  - Fitness, gyms, Jazzerize [sic], etc., Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 10)
  - Hot Pants, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 11)
  - Industry, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 12-13)
  - Original News Clips of King City Rustler, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 14)
  - Metropolitan MOMA, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 15)
  - Masquerade/Costumes, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 16)
  - New Years, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 17)
  - New Yorker People, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 18)
  - Good contemp. topics for playboy, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 19)
  - Playboy Words, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 20)
  - Psychiatry/Psychoanalysis, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 21)
  - Punk Music, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 22)
  - Rock Groups, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 23)
  - Rock and Roll, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 24)
  - William Steig, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 25)
  - Sylph Bronson, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 26)
  - Tales of New York, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 27)
  - Teens: Protest Rock and Roll, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 28)
  - Think Pics, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 29)
  - Writers at Work, Undated (Box ED 50, Folder 30)
  - Articles on Soviet Union, Communist Bloc, 1989 (Box ED 51, Folder 1)
  - Art, Pivotal articles, Undated (Box ED 51, Folder 2)
  - Cubism, Undated (Box ED 51, Folder 3)
  - Japan, Undated (Box ED 51, Folder 4)
  - Japanese Architecture, Undated (Box ED 51, Folder 5)
  - Jazz, Undated (Box ED 51, Folder 6-10)
  - Joe Camel, Undated (Box ED 51, Folder 11)
  - Clips on local people, Undated (Box ED 51, Folder 12)
  - Clips on local events, Undated (Box ED 51, Folder 13)
  - Read, Re-read, Save Articles, Undated (Box ED 51, Folder 14)
  - Russia, 1989 (Box ED 51, Folder 15)
  - Maurice Sendak, 1980 (Box ED 51, Folder 16)
  - Ticino, photos & articles, Undated (Box ED 51, Folder 17-18)